gigats.com 2015-06-13

# Gigats Privacy Policy

### Gigats (the "Company") takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This policy describes the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of the Company and applies to the Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by the Company on its Websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), on various third party websites, and to the Company's other information collection. The Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Company does not own or control or to people that the Company does not employ or manage.

**Collection and Use of Your Information**   
The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company, when you use the Company's products or services, when you visit the Company's pages or the pages of certain of the Company's partners. The Company may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, physical address, and telephone number(s). When you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

The Company automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

The aforementioned information may be made available to the Company's clients, affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this website or for our business. The Company's clients, affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties may also disclose such information to third parties they retain to provide products or services based on their own terms of service agreements.

We may use third parties to help operate our website and deliver products and services, and may share your personal information with our clients' affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties (such as Website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, payment services, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). **Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us in providing you with products or services requested of us or our affiliates by you.** When you conduct e-commerce with one of the e-commerce affiliates or service providers to which the website may be linked, certain personal information such as your email and home address may be collected by the service provider's server and made available to us.

By using the Websites and participating in an interview with a Company Specialist you are consenting that the recording of the interview may be shared as follows: with any prospective employer upon the employer's request; among the Company's staff for evaluation of quality and service; and with our clients, affiliates, advertisers, service providers, potential employers and other third parties that provide products or services for us or by us for them. You will be given the opportunity to object to the sharing of this recording with our clients, affiliates, advertisers, service providers, and other third parties that provide products or services for us or by us for them. If a request is made of the Company to share the recording, the Company will send an email message to the email address you have provided. You shall have 72 hours to object to the request. If, after 72 hours, you have not objected to the requested disclosure, the Company will release the recording.

The Company only releases your information to third parties for the purposes listed above, except where required by law.

You should be aware, however, that when you choose to display or distribute personal information such as your email address or resume via the Websites or any other distribution method, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which the Company is not responsible.

You should take measures to protect your personal information when distributing resumes via the Websites, or any other channels unrelated to the Company, for that matter. Best practices include never giving your social security number to a prospective employer. Employers only need that information _after_ they have hired you. Never provide credit card or bank numbers or engage in a monetary transaction of any sort with prospective employers. Be cautious when dealing with contacts outside of your own country. Do not provide any non-work related personal information (i.e. social security number, date of birth, eye color, marital status, etc.) over the phone or online.

**Cookies**   
Some pages on this Website employ browser session "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data that a Website transfers to your computer's hard disk to allow the server to distinguish your session from that of others while you are connected. Requests to send cookies are not designed to collect information about you, but only about your "browser session." The cookies make it easier for you to use the dynamic features of our Website. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Website security**   
Security is a priority at the Company. Appropriate measures are taken to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information about our members, providers, employers, brokers, and anyone else that may want to use our Website.

Only authorized users are allowed to access the information. The Company enforces a high level of protection, i.e., 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, for securing transmissions between a user's browser and this Website. Content on this site is protected against unauthorized access.

**Email security**   
Email sent over the Internet is not secure and should not be used to communicate confidential information to the Company. Please be aware that the Company cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of any information you send to us over the Internet when using email. The Company shall not be liable for any breach of confidentiality resulting from such use of email via the Internet. The Company will not use email to communicate confidential information unless the email is secured in accordance with the Company Corporate Email Policy.

**Email Anti-Spam Policy:**   
The Company does not send unsolicited commercial email through our systems. If you believe you have received an unsolicited commercial email from the Company on behalf of any of our advertisers, please send an email (with the reported unsolicited commercial email included or attached with the 'full header') to: [spamreport@gigats.com](mailto:spamreport@gigats.com).

**Unsubscribe Policy**   
To unsubscribe from the Company's email lists, a person must send an email to [unsubscribe@gigats.com](mailto:unsubscribe@gigats.com). Our unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by the Company on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of third parties and your personal information may still be shared with third parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.

Unsubscribing from our electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the information from third parties. Since third parties maintain separate databases from us you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

**Your California Privacy Rights**   
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@gigats.com](mailto:privacy@gigats.com). In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).

**No Information Collected from Children.**   
The Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, the Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. The Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

**Third Party Advertising**   
Ads appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by the Company, or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements they believe will be of most interest to you.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**   
This privacy policy changes from time to time and changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. We do not provide notices of changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this Website.
